<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pablo Benavides on PBenavides</title>
    <link>https://pbenavides.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pablo Benavides on PBenavides</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pbenavides.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automated Valuation Model - Lima</title>
      <link>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>About the Project This project started in 2019 when I was trying to practice my web-scraping and Machine learning skills. It was the first personal project that I had been involved in, and it even was a start-up project idea that couldn&amp;rsquo;t be accomplished for many reasons. I learnt a lot from this and I dedicated a great amount of time to iterate over the ideas. Suddenly, it ended up being a Spatial Data Science project due to the advantage of the scraped data: geographically coordinates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experimentation Notebooks</title>
      <link>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>These are Proof of Concept Notebooks where I&amp;rsquo;m replicating some tutorials or articles with my point of view or own data. I built this notebooks to keep a record of which use-cases I could make in the future and as personal note-taking of the topics that I&amp;rsquo;ve studied. Some of the topics I&amp;rsquo;m including in this notebooks are:
  Data_visualization: A calendar plot about USDPEN prices.
  FeatureEncoding Challenge: Kaggle competition about encoding techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on the part of the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Introductory Course</title>
      <link>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FX Derivatives Portfolio Optimizer</title>
      <link>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>In Progress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lima - Real Estate Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pbenavides.github.io/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://pbenavides.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pbenavides.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>This is an example of a custom shortcode that you can put right into your content. You will need to add a form action to the the shortcode to make it work. Check out Formspree for a simple, free form service.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
